(Yugo) Didn't you notice?
Since the first time we met ➡
forever
I was curious about you. ➡
Not the president ➡
I want you to choose me. ➡
Because I'm serious.
♬〜
(Hattori Maika) Sorry.
(Yugo) I don't have to hurry to reply. ➡
It's going to be a long battle
I'm prepared.
(Yugo) See you tomorrow.
♬〜
(Akiyama) President.
(Satori Shun) Is that what it was like?
Hmm...
(Yugo) Are you finished?
Ah yes.
(Yugo)
I'm finished too so I'll send it.
Ah, no, it's fine.
(Yugo) Maybe ➡
Are you aware of me?
Ah, that's not the case...
If it were Yugo...
It's exactly as Kato said.
For Shun
There's a lot I have.
that's why
I want to be Shun's support.
I want to be strong.
I want to work harder and harder at work.
So...➡
sorry.
I'm in the time of a change of heart
There's none.
(Yugo) I'm really jealous of you. ➡
I hate it.
📱(Manner mode)
Huh?
Tap (operation sound)
president
Hattori-san I can't take my hands off now.
Oh, ah, ah, ah
What are you doing on your own?
(Yugo)
I won't give anything to him anymore.
Ah...
(Yugo) Absolutely...➡
I'll definitely make you mine.
Ah, a bit
Oh... Kato-san, let it go!
⚟What are you doing?
Ha ha ha ha... Hmm!
Are you okay?
Shun-san, why are you here?
I'll talk later.
♬〜
What am I doing
Do you know?
♬〜
It's all about my mother's instructions
I know.
But I'm
I can't forgive what you're doing.
♬〜
What does it mean?
I'm a little worried
I tried to find out about him.
There is evidence that I'm connected to my mother
It came out in a mess.
My mother used him ➡
We
I was about to break up.
I also got closer to Maika
That's why.
Kato-san, is it true?
(Yugo) Hmm... haha. ➡
Was it discovered?
(Yugo) This is quickly
I thought I could finish it. ➡
Hattori-san
The guard is surprisingly strong ➡
It's more effort than expected.
♬〜
Why
Kato-san is like that...
(Yugo)
Because I didn't like it.
♬〜
(Yugo) The same blood flows ➡
Benefits of everything
You are living a sigh.
What's that about?
Me and you ➡
They were born from the same mother.
Me and you
He's a half-brother.
♬〜
No, I don't think I have a brother
I've never heard of it.
(Yugo) Of course that's true. ➡
I'm
Because that person abandoned me.
It was abandoned...
(Yugo) He was put in a facility.
(Yugo) When I was 3 years old
A new man has been created. ➡
The man at that time was probably
Isn't it your father?
I don't think I remember, but I...
Just once to you
I've met you before. ➡
At the facility by chance➡
I saw my mother's new address ➡
I want to see my mother ➡
That day
I went to visit alone. ➡
I'll be my mother someday
I myself
I believed he would come and pick me up. ➡
But after entering the facility
My mother has never been
He didn't come to see me.
(Photons, recollection)
｟Here it is quick. Heheh
(Yugo)Mom｠
(Yugo)
To be honest, I also had a vague recollection of his face...
(Mitsuko) Yugo? ｠
(Yugo) Take a look ➡
I knew it was my mother.
(Yugo) Mother! ｠
♬〜
｟Mom, who is that child? ｠
⦅here we go? Maybe you're lost. ➡
I went straight to that road
Because there's a police box ➡
If you're unsure, go and try it. ➡
Now, let's go, Shun
(Yugo)
I understood it clearly.
I was abandoned.
Then I don't know more.
You must be grudge against your mother
Why did you cooperate?
(Yugo) First up ➡
I'm willing to cooperate
There wasn't. ➡
What's more, ever since then➡
Even your location
I didn't know.
(Yugo) That's a few months ago➡
Suddenly I was called.
｟♬~(BGM in the store)｠
｟It's been a while, Yugo｠
｟I look good, I'm happy｠
｟♬~(BGM in the store)｠
｟You remembered my name｠
｟Hehe I remember
Isn't it decided?
｟I'm glad you've become so impressive｠
⦅I agree⦆
｟The people at the facility
Thanks to your kindness
Somehow
I'm living as a working adult
(Photons)
｟That's right. I can't believe you're
I don't think I'm working for my company
｟And also a talented employee
He's even been awarded?
｟ "My company"? ｠
｟Oh, haven't you heard it? ｠
｟I remarried.
About 10 years ago ➡
With the chairman of "Satori Holdings"
｟♬~(BGM in the store)｠
｟So ➡
What is the current president, Satori Shun?
That time...｠
(Photons)
｟I feel lonely to you➡
I've let it go. ➡
I'm really sorry.
But there was no choice.
｟At that time
I was young and had no money.
I was desperate to live
｟Huh...
It's not important now
｟To say that
Did you call? ｠
｟Isn't it?｠
｟In fact, to you
There's something I want to cooperate with
｟What is it? ｠
(Hiko)｟Your brother ➡
A crazy woman
It got caught. ➡
Shun is the president. ➡
But a woman who is not very knowledgeable ➡
Seduce my precious son
I've lost it
｟To marry a woman like this
Can you be forced to?
｟Shun has a better marriage
There are so many
｟So for me
What do you say you should do? ｠
(Photon)｟You
He really grew up so cool ➡
Even within the company, from female employees
It doesn't seem to be popular
(Hiko)｟This ordinary woman➡
Isn't it easy to drop? ｠
♬〜
(Yugo)
I've been leaving it alone until now➡
You're using me...
That's what I thought. ➡
Conversely, me too
I'll use it as much as possible➡
Because I thought so
I took it on.
♬〜
(Yugo) It's true that first
Because my mother told me
I've come near you. ➡
But it's not right now. ➡
I'm serious about you...
Don't get close to her.
♬〜
you
I have everything ➡
Even if you give me one
That's fine!
If that's Maika ➡
That's impossible.
Whether it's not possible
I don't know yet.
♬〜
Sorry for today.
(Yugo) Hattori-san See you tomorrow.
Shun-san.
please.
Ah...
Ah, thank you.
OK?
Yeah.
But I'm a little confused...
I can't believe I had a brother.
Why was your mother silent?
Abandoning my biological child
I'm not going to use that brother.
One person
I should have lived in peace.
This is what happens because of me...
Shun-san...
I knew he was a selfish person.
Still ➡
to this point
Because he raised me...
I intend to repay my mother and father-in-law
I've come to my best.
Sorry for getting involved in this.
Because I'm fine.
I've sorted my mind a little bit ➡
Think about how you'll deal with it...
Don't take it on your own.
♬〜
If it's difficult, please refer to it.
thank you.
♬〜
Ugh...
(Nozomi)
Yes, it's over It's over.
(Male employee) Lunch Where are you going?
(Nozomi) Ahhh ➡
Where shall we go?
Hattori-san will also go with me.
Ah yes.
(Male employee) Yes, it's here.
(Voice in the heart) <Kato-san, always
I'm sure you've been having a hard time
But Shun, who learned the truth
I'm really suffering≫
<What should I do? ≫
<What can I do? ≫
Konkon
Excuse me.
Sorry for taking the time to do so.
The president's direct
It's a call.
I did a DNA test.
You are after all ➡
Being my brother
It seems there's no doubt.
Work is quick.
The facilities too➡
I looked into it.
Maybe
You were involved in my mother's role➡
The facility where you grew up➡
Because I want to help
What's that?
♬〜
(Hiko)｟This ordinary woman➡
Isn't it easy to drop? ｠
｟I refuse
｟Works quite a bit
I'm not struggling with my life
｟Yugo ➡
You're the only one who's not in trouble
Is that okay? ｠
(Yugo) What? ｠
｟I've been helping you for a long time
Child welfare facilities ➡
Due to financial difficulties, there is a plan to demolish it
You know there is, right? ｠
♬〜
If that's the case ➡
If it's okay
Please help me.
Quite a lot
You're falling in love with her.
If you're a president, then you're the other person
There must be so many that it rots.
(Yugo)
Why did you go out of your way to Hattori-san?
This is how it is
Even if unexpected events occur ➡
Without shaking
You can stand straight ➡
It's definitely thanks to her.
she
He's an important person to me.
Hmm...
Blood cannot be fought.
Huh?
For me too
She is a loved one.
So make your suggestion
I'm not going to do anything.
♬〜
I decided not to hold back anymore.
I'll get everything I want.
Please wait a minute!
Brother!
When I'm having a hard time...
At times like this
If there's a brother who can talk about anything ➡
How good it would be ➡
I've thought about it many times.
I know you're my brother ➡
I'm happy.
So ➡
If you're suffering
I want to help.
♬〜
Because it's family.
Bang (the sound of the doer)
♬〜
⚟Try and work...(Footsteps)
Kato-san.
Hattori-san.
Thank you for your hard work.
Ah... that's good.
Today is already
I was hoping I could not go back.
Was he waiting for me?
yes.
I want to talk.
What are you talking about?
I….
For Shun-san too...
For Kato-san too...
more than this
I don't want you to suffer.
The two are family...
I don't want you to fight.
How the two of them can reconcile
Isn't it?
So the solution is
You're presenting it, right? ➡
Even if I withdraw my hand ➡
That person is
I won't acknowledge you guys. ➡
I'll try to get in the way again.
Every time, the president
It's going to cause pain.
♬〜
The two of them
By trying to stick to your feelings...
♬〜
It makes many people unhappy.
(Yugo) You
If you really think of him ➡
Please show your determination.
｟ Become a fake lover with me ➡
Would you like to look back at the two of you? ｠
｟Eh? ｠
>
He was a false lover≫
(Narimitsu) ｟Answer! ｠
When it's painful
Have a lot of help...≫
｟I've been saved by you again
⦅thank you⦆
｟I like it｠
⦅ Understand the length of your body⦆
⦅Don't get close to her⦆
<<I'm now
What can you do for Shun?
What he carries on his shoulders➡
Make it lighter as much as possible
Maybe it is≫
♬〜
Understood.
I'm breaking up with Shun.
Listen to my selfishness
thank you.
What mom says
If you listen ➡
I could be happy though.
Why are you
Are you crying about us?
I'm happy enough now.